prudential insurance scams in texas city
texas if you want the absolute lowest
price possible for auto insurance you
need to know the minimum auto insurance
coverage required by your state each
state has different minimum requirements
so you'll need to go to your state's
department of insurance website to find
out the requirements for your state when
you see insurance requirements they will
typically be in a format like this 2045.
what do these numbers mean
well the first two numbers are for
bodily injury limits this is the amount
an insurance company will pay for
injuries in an accident the first number
is the per person limit and the second
number is the accident limit in this
example the insurance company will pay
up to
20.000 per person injured in an accident
but no more than
40.000 total for all people injured the
third number is the property damage
coverage in our example the insurance
company would pay
5.000 for property damage while the
minimum insurance requirements may seem
like a lot they really don't offer much
coverage if you caused an accident that
injured someone their medical bills
could very quickly surpass your
insurance if all you have is the minimum
required amounts then you're left
vulnerable to lawsuits and having to pay
the rest of the amount out of your own
pocket it is far better to choose higher
coverage amounts and try to save on your
insurance in other ways for example you
can go online to get free quotes from
insurance comparison websites because
companies on these websites are
competing for your business you'll find
the quotes are cheap if you choose your
insurance wisely you can afford to
increase your coverages beyond the
minimum requirements